STUART:
Oh, good. Good.
(Stuart:)I love you.
(Leonard:)I'm not leaving until you talk to me.
-Hey, what's going on?
-It's a little hard to explain.
(Leonard:)He pretends
he's in an alternate dimension...
(Leonard:)...that occupies the same physical space
we're in, but he can't perceive us.
(Sheldon:)Don't flatter yourself.
I'm just ignoring you.
All right, come on, Sheldon,
let's go home. We're done fighting.
(Sheldon:)I've heard that before.
(Sheldon:)Then the next thing you know,
I'm hiding in my bedroom...
...blaring a Richard Feynman lecture,
Mom shouting Jesus would forgive her...
(Sheldon:)...if she put ground glass
in my dad's meat loaf.
And my dad's on the roof skeet shooting
her Franklin Mint collectible plates.
Okay, there's gonna be no more shouting
and no skeet shooting.
(Sheldon:)Really? Where's your friend Justin
going to sleep?
-Yeah, where is he gonna sleep?
-Oh, my God, would you let this go?
(Stuart:)I'd let it go.
(Leonard:)Why should I let it go? Why don't you
just tell the guy to find a place to sleep?